What if you wanted to make the first paragraph bold,
如果你想让第一个段落变成粗体
with a larger font,
且使用更大的字体
and then the last two paragraphs with an italic font.
然后最后两段用斜体 该怎么做?
To change the font and font style, you'll need CSS.
要更改字体和字体样式 你需要 CSS
But we're not quite ready yet to add CSS styling.
但我们还没完全准备好添加 CSS 样式
You'll need to differentiate between the first paragraph and the other paragraphs.
你需要先区分第一个段落和其他段落
HTML has attributes specifically for differentiating elements from each other,
HTML 具有专门用于区分元素的属性
the ID attribute and the class attribute.
id 属性和 class 属性
IDs uniquely identify a piece of content.
id 可以唯一标识一段内容
For example, I can use an ID in the first paragraph to add ID equals P top.
比如 我可以在第一段中添加 id="p_top"
As you'll see later in this lesson,
正如你将在本课后面看到的
you can now pick out the P top paragraph and add a bold font just to that paragraph.
现在就可以选中 p_top 段落并且只为该段落添加粗体样式
An ID is a unique identifier that you should only use once per HTML page.
id 是唯一标识符 每个 HTML 页面只能使用一次
You can name IDs whatever you want,
你可以随意命名 id
but you should only use the name once,
但应该只使用一次该名称
and the tag should only have one ID.
并且标签应该只有一个 id
So, the paragraph tag can only have that P Top ID.
因此 段落标签只能拥有这个 p_top id
I'll add a few other IDs to reinforce this.
我将添加一些其他 id 来强化理解
So, for example, the middle paragraph can be P middle,
比如 中间的段落可以是 p_middle
and the bottom P bottom.
底部段落是 p_bottom
I'm going to add IDs to the div tags as well.
我也要为 div 标签添加 id
Like ID equals link section and ID equals paragraph section.
比如 id="links_section" 以及 id="paragraphs_section"
Like I said, IDs can go in any tag.
我之前说过 id 可以放在任何标签中
Each element can have one ID,
每个元素可以有一个 id
and each ID name should be unique.
每个 id 名称应该是唯一的
The idea is that you're separating out the content for different CSS styling.
这个思路是 你要分离出不同的内容应用不同的样式
Classes on the other hand,
另一方面 class 属性
group multiple pieces of content together.
将多个内容组合在一起
So, for example I could add a class to these two bottom paragraphs called italic text.
因此 我可以在这两个底部段落中添加一个 class 称为 italic_text
Implying that I'm going to style these two paragraphs with an italic font.
暗示我将用斜体字体设置这两个段落的样式
You can name a class whatever you want,
你可以随意命名 class
and you can use a class name multiple times in
一个 HTML 文档可以多次使用一个 class 名称
an HTML document in order to group pieces of content together.
以便将多个内容组合在一起
An element can even have more than one class.
一个元素甚至可以有多个 class
Like I could add another class called green text.
就像我可以添加另一个名为 green_text 的 class
Implying I'm going to style this last paragraph green.
暗示我要将这最后一段应用为绿色
I could have the same green text class to a link.
我可以将同一个 green_text 类添加到一个链接中
Adding IDs and classes will give you more control over your website's CSS styling,
添加 id 和 class 可以让你更好地控制网站的 CSS 样式
they help you add style to your pages in a logical organized way.
可以帮助你以逻辑性的合理方式为页面添加样式
In the next exercise,
在下一个练习中
you'll get practice adding div and span tags,
你会练习添加 div 和 span 标签
as well as using classes and IDs.
以及使用 class 和 id